bookswim.com 2013-03-21

# Book Rental - BookSwim

Bestselling books, delivered to your door.

### We hate spam too

BookSwim.com is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of our members. Throughout cyberspace, we want to contribute to providing a safe and secure environment for consumers, and in particular, ensure that children (i.e. anyone who is under the age of 18) are protected from inappropriate materials. The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform you, as a welcome visitor to BookSwim.com, what kinds of information we may gather about you when you visit www.bookswim.com, how we may use that information,whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct the information.

We offer membership services only to consumers over the age of 18. We do not knowingly collect data from minors.

## Information About You

Upon registration for membership, BookSwim.com will specifically ask for information about you. We will ask for your full name, billing address, telephone number and credit card number in order to ship you your products and provide you with all of BookSwim.com's services. We may ask for demographic information from you to help make our service more useful to you. We use your telephone number only if there is an order-related issue, though because we understand your need for anonymity we will make all attempts to contact you via email. We do not use your telephone number for marketing purposes. Our database stores this information so that placing future orders will be quicker and easier. If you want to update your address or change credit cards, go to your BookSwim.com personal page and make the appropriate changes. We may also use that information to let you know of additional products and services about which you might be interested. You can choose not to receive such information if you don't want to by letting us know on the registration screen when you sign up for our service. We may ask you for information about your interests so that both you and we can take advantage of the interactivity of the online medium, but you may always choose to not respond.

## Tracking Information

BookSwim.com will collect and store only the following non-personally-identifying information from you: the name of the domain name from which you access the Internet; the date and time you access our site; and the Internet address of the Website from which you linked directly to our site. We also track your order and billing history so you can access your Account at BookSwim.com and immediately determine which Books you've rented and how you paid for them. This information is also used to remove rented titles from your Book Request List. This information is password-protected. No one has access to it but you.

As you browse the BookSwim.com site, cookies are placed on your computer's hard drive. Cookies allow us to track the items you select as you shop, and help us match your address and credit card information with your order so you don't need to retype the information each time you visit our site. Cookies also allow us to gather information to provide you with the best service. It tells us the number and frequency of visitors to our site and its various pages. Third parties may serve some of these cookies. We analyze this data to determine which parts of our site customers like and which parts need improvement. Automatically logged information is also used to analyze trends and to administer the site.

The only party that we may share your transaction processing information is PayPal, which subsequently may share that information to a third party licensor of the fraud prevention scoring services (the "Fraud Service Bureau") solely for use in developing its fraud prevention modeling and for performing the Fraud Services. All your transaction processing information provided to the Fraud Service Bureau shall be subject to written agreement between PayPal and the Fraud Service Bureau restricting disclosure of any Customer Data to other third parties except as necessary to perform the Fraud Services. Otherwise, all of your personal information such as name, address, email address and telephone number will not be shared with any third parties.

## Disclosure 

We do not use or disclose information about your individual visits to BookSwim.com or your personal information as described above, to any third parties. We may however share aggregated statistical information with our partners about the use of BookSwim.com. Any exceptions to this policy of sharing your name, address or email address with a partner company will be done only with your permission.

## Security And Access 

BookSwim.com uses a secure socket layer (SSL), which encrypts all information that is transmitted or received. This encryption process ensures that the information you give us is protected against unauthorized access.

You can access Your Account from every page on the site to update and correct your name, email address, password, postal address, credit cards, mailing list preferences, and your Book Request List.

We have implemented technology and security features, as well as strict internal guidelines, to safeguard the privacy of your personal information from unauthorized access or improper use. We will continue to enhance our security procedures as new technology becomes available. While we make every effort to ensure that your information is secure on our system, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

As a convenience to its members, BookSwim may refresh expired credit card or debit card numbers with the numbers of replacement cards so that members' paid Services do not lapse because the payment instrument initially on file with BookSwim has expired ("Account Updater"). By registering for the Service, you consent to BookSwim's disclosure of your registration information to your financial institution and to that institution's use of such information solely in connection with Account Updater. You also consent to BookSwim's receipt and use of updated credit card or debit card account information from your financial institution in connection with the provision of the Service as provided in the TOS, these Additional Terms, and the BookSwim Privacy Policy. 

## BOOKSWIM.COM PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES 

If we decide to change our privacy policy for BookSwim.com, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone.

## Contact 

If you have any questions concerning our privacy policy you can contact us through our [contact form](http://bookswim.com/contact.html) or mail us at:

**BookSwim Corporation**   
Attn: Customer Service   
211 Warren Street  
Suite 305  
Newark, NJ 07103  
**Email:**  
**Facsimile:** 732-653-0296 

Want more info? Browse our frequently asked questions here.

© 2007-2010 BookSwim, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
